trvid.com 2008-03-12

# TravelerVideos.com - Watch Thousands of Free Unbiased Video Travel Guides.

TravelerVideos Video Privacy Notice 

The TravelerVideos Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information when you use TravelerVideos`s products and services, including information provided when you use the TravelerVideos Video Player. The following are our privacy practices that are specific to the TravelerVideos Video Player.

Personal information

You can download free videos from TravelerVideos Video without having a TravelerVideos Account or providing account information to TravelerVideos.   
You need a TravelerVideos Account to purchase content to play on the TravelerVideos Video Player. TravelerVideos asks for some personal information when you create a TravelerVideos Account, including a user ID and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. A TravelerVideos Account allows you to access many of our services that require registration.   
TravelerVideos takes steps to protect copyrighted content by embedding the TravelerVideos Account information of the person who downloads each copy-protected video, in encrypted form, in the video itself. When you play a copy-protected video, the Player will send this encrypted information to TravelerVideos, including the identity of the video, to confirm that the copy is authorized.

When you download free videos or play 3rd party deliverd videos, no account information will be embedded in the video. Windows-compatible Video Players may contact TravelerVideos`s servers to finalize the download process when you play the video.

TravelerVideos receives standard log information when the Player contacts TravelerVideos`s servers during the download process and when confirming authorization to view copy-protected content.

Uses   
In addition to using Account information to protect copyrighted content, we use information about aggregate Video Player usage to improve the quality of the Player and other TravelerVideos services.

Information sharing and onward transfer

We may share aggregate statistics about video downloads and other TravelerVideos Video Player usage with our business partners. We will not share personally identifying information with these partners or any third parties.

Your choices

You can terminate your TravelerVideos Account at any time as described here.

More information

TravelerVideos adheres to the US Safe Harbor privacy principles. For more information about the Safe Harbor framework or our registration, see the Department of Commerce`s web site. Further information about the TravelerVideos Video Player is available here.  
For more information about our privacy practices, go to the full privacy policy. If you have additional questions, please contact us any time. Or write to us at:  
Privacy Matters  
c/o TravelerVideos   
PO Box 1452  
Boston, MA  01742 (USA)
